Guide to the Hans Horst Meyer papers, 1831-1943, 2004 and undated RL.00894
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Dr. Arthur Meyer memorabilia relating to Czar Boris III of Bulgaria, 1917-1943; 30 items 1 flat box
  - Set of 15 stereoscopic black-and-white diapositive slides with wooden box viewer, bearing images of Boris III, family, and retinue, and portraits of Hans Horst Meyer with grandson (Horst?), 1920s-1930s (Box 10)
    Glass slides are in popular 45x107 mm size; the photographer is unknown. Images show Boris III riding in car with driver; a picnic party with Boris III and family; portraits of Boris III and family members; and a series of portraits of Hans Horst Meyer, circa 1935, seated, with grandson Horst?